[SPEAKER_00] Hello?
[SPEAKER_01] Good day, Chris. This is Ron. How are you doing, my man?
[SPEAKER_00] Good, and you, Ron?
[SPEAKER_01] I'm doing great. Is that a good time to talk, or are you around by any chance?
[SPEAKER_00] Mate, I've got quarter past. I've got ten minutes, then I'm going for that interview that they postponed on Friday.
[SPEAKER_01] Ah, okay, okay, okay. No worries. I just want to double-check with you one thing, okay?
[SPEAKER_01] So we're not having a long conversation now.
[SPEAKER_01] You wrote me that you have 64,000 US inside Binance and 50,000 Australian dollars inside SwiftX, right?
[SPEAKER_01] Yes.
[SPEAKER_01] But it should be wrong. I mean, you should have more than that.
[SPEAKER_00] In where?
[SPEAKER_00] You need to have more...
[SPEAKER_00] I transferred on Friday, Saturday and Sunday.
[SPEAKER_00] 48, 48 and 48 over.
[SPEAKER_01] Okay, and before that we transfer as well, like 50. So you need to have like 200,000 Australian dollars inside Binance.
[SPEAKER_01] And 70 grand around... even more right now because the crypto market skyrocketed high.
[SPEAKER_01] So I need to have like 80 around inside SwiftX. That's why it doesn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_01] And I wanted to ring you to double-check. Are you able to connect with me?
[SPEAKER_01] Yeah, for like one, two minutes. Just to double-check that everything is okay.
[SPEAKER_01] Alright.
[SPEAKER_01] We are standing in a very good time. I don't know if you follow whatever happened in the crypto market.
[SPEAKER_01] It just skyrocketed in high quite a lot.
[SPEAKER_01] We had massive news that happens and comes from Trump.
[SPEAKER_01] We're not going to confuse you before your interview because I wonder if you will be prepared and fully on the interview.
[SPEAKER_01] And I will share with you that later on tonight.
[SPEAKER_01] But let's just double-check and making sure that everything is in the right place.
[SPEAKER_01] I don't want that... I don't know if you will have any hacking or anything like that or someone took money from the exchange.
[SPEAKER_00] Okay.
[SPEAKER_01] And security code is CO2005.
[SPEAKER_00] Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_00] Oh sorry.
[SPEAKER_01] Yeah, and sign in, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01] That's James.
[SPEAKER_00] Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01] Depends to the best of us.
[SPEAKER_00] Dashboard.
[SPEAKER_01] Okay.
[SPEAKER_01] Overall performance, 4,301.
[SPEAKER_01] Can I take over real quick?
[SPEAKER_00] Yep.
[SPEAKER_01] One second.
[SPEAKER_01] So we see you have more than 50.
[SPEAKER_01] You wrote that you have 50, mate.
[SPEAKER_00] Yeah, there's 50 days.
[SPEAKER_01] The others...
[SPEAKER_00] Ah, no.
[SPEAKER_01] No, I was talking about the overall portfolio, my man.
[SPEAKER_01] Not about the amount of...
[SPEAKER_01] Ah.
[SPEAKER_00] All right.
[SPEAKER_00] I got you.
[SPEAKER_00] But remember there's other stuff that we sit on triggers?
[SPEAKER_01] Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01] Can you just approve my request?
[SPEAKER_01] I asked you about the balance because the crypto market skyrocketed high over the weekend.
[SPEAKER_01] So you see, 7%, 7%, 8%, 6%.
[SPEAKER_01] So I asked you about the balance to understand.
[SPEAKER_01] Okay.
[SPEAKER_01] What is the situation?
[SPEAKER_01] So that's good.
[SPEAKER_01] We have 50K outside the market.
[SPEAKER_01] Yep.
[SPEAKER_01] I will buy...
[SPEAKER_01] I will buy a little bit more over here.
[SPEAKER_01] Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00] Just check the triggers.
[SPEAKER_00] Is that coming through the money?
[SPEAKER_01] It will not be triggered.
[SPEAKER_01] I mean, all the crypto markets skyrocketed high.
[SPEAKER_01] There is no way that it will be triggered.
[SPEAKER_01] Market is boiling, my man.
[SPEAKER_01] So I wanted to share with you a few things, but I forgot that you have interview right now.
[SPEAKER_01] So all good.
[SPEAKER_01] Just spoke with you a little bit more crypto.
[SPEAKER_01] Let's go over to wallet again.
[SPEAKER_00] What about Trump?
[SPEAKER_01] Trump, 8%, mate.
[SPEAKER_00] Up.
[SPEAKER_00] Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01] See?
[SPEAKER_01] Ethereum, 8%.
[SPEAKER_01] XRP, 3%.
[SPEAKER_01] 7% Solana.
[SPEAKER_01] Bitcoin.
[SPEAKER_01] Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01] Okay.
[SPEAKER_01] Go to...
[SPEAKER_01] We finished with SwiftX for now.
[SPEAKER_01] Go to Binance.
[SPEAKER_01] Let me just double check that everything is correct over there.
[SPEAKER_00] Yes, Binance.
[SPEAKER_00] I already logged in.
[SPEAKER_00] And I was looking at this.
[SPEAKER_00] Also what?
[SPEAKER_01] Ethereum.
[SPEAKER_01] You already Ethereum on your SwiftX account.
[SPEAKER_01] I bought with you Friday.
[SPEAKER_01] Okay.
[SPEAKER_01] I will take over.
[SPEAKER_01] Take you to the right place.
[SPEAKER_00] Oh shit.
[SPEAKER_01] Oh shit.
[SPEAKER_01] 7,000 Australian after all the fees
[SPEAKER_01] that you paid just until now.
[SPEAKER_01] Roughly around 3%.
[SPEAKER_01] Just until now.
[SPEAKER_01] Okay?
[SPEAKER_01] More to come. I will share with you all
[SPEAKER_01] the information later on today.
[SPEAKER_01] We are probably going to make a big move
[SPEAKER_01] as well on Trump coin.
[SPEAKER_01] Trump is going to come with a big statement.
[SPEAKER_01] So I will share that with you.
[SPEAKER_01] We scheduled a call for
[SPEAKER_01] 7 o'clock
[SPEAKER_01] later on tonight.
[SPEAKER_01] If you are around
[SPEAKER_01] before, shoot me a text.
[SPEAKER_01] Alright. I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_01] Beautiful, my man. And good luck
[SPEAKER_01] in the interview, my man. All the best.
[SPEAKER_00] Thanks, Ron. Speak to you later then.
[SPEAKER_01] Speak to you later. Bye, my mate.
[SPEAKER_00] Yes, man. Bye.